mobogenie.com 2018-01-18

# Mobogenie: All-in-one Android Smartphone PC Manager

This Privacy Policy applies to the website www.mobogenie.com and other websites associated with such URL (collectively the "Website") powered by Gamease Age Digital Technology Co., Ltd.("The Company"). By using the Website, you consent to the practices described herein. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect company and customer feedback. You should periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed of our practices. Your continued use of the Website following any changes to this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of those changes.

Collection of your Personal Information

The Company may collect through some portions of the Website personal identifiable information, such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address ("Personal Information"). We may also collect anonymous demographic and usage pattern information which is not unique to you, such as your geographic area, age, gender, preferences, interests, favorites, log-in frequency, purchase history, and usage history. This demographic and usage pattern information is not considered Personal Information except when it is used in conjunction with other information that personally identifies you.

When you access or use the Website and any features contained therein, we also automatically collect technical information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring web site addresses, etc. This technical information is not considered Personal Information except when it is used in conjunction with other information that personally identifies you.

We may aggregate your demographic and/or technical information to help us understand our users' trends and needs, and to improve the quality of our services. Such aggregated data will remove personally-identifying information and will not be considered Personal Information.

Please keep in mind that any information you post on or send through the Website's discussion forums, chat rooms, or messaging functions is publicly available and not confidential. If you disclose your Personal Information or other personally sensitive data through such channels, it may be collected and used by others, and The Company shall not be liable for any resulting claims, losses, or damages.

Please also note that when you visit third-party websites linked to or from the Website, any information you disclose on those third-party websites is subject to their privacy policies and practices. The Company shall not be responsible for the practices of any third-party websites. You should carefully review each third-party website's privacy policy.

What other types of information may we collect?

For some activities, we may ask you to create a user name and password and/or to provide other, non-personal information such as your age, date of birth, gender, and/or game and platform preferences; and, combine such information with your personal information. In addition, your web browser or client software may transmit certain geographic information or information regarding your computer (capabilities, game data processing, etc.) to The Company. The Company may use this information to generate aggregate statistics about our user community and may provide such information to advertisers and/or our partners. In addition, The Company may use such information for security, system integrity (the prevention of hacking, cheats, etc.), or enforcement purposes. From time to time, we may also post customer testimonials that contain personally identifiable information on The Company's websites. However, we will obtain the customer's consent to post these testimonials prior to publication in accordance with the applicable Terms of Services (TOS).

Use of your Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to: (a) operate the Website and provide the services we offer; (b) deliver the services you request; (c) provide technical support; (d) verify any online payment, telephone payment, and pre-paid card transactions, which are solely processed through third-party service providers with their own privacy policies for which we are not responsible; (e) investigate alleged fraud, infringement, or other misconduct; (f) send you newsletters; and (g) inform you about other products, services, events, and promotions available from The Company or its affiliates. We may also use your Personal Information to contact you via surveys or other research regarding your opinion of any current and potential services.

We may share Personal Information with our service providers who need access to such information in order to complete the work they have been engaged to do. In some cases, such service providers may directly collect Personal Information from you on our behalf. Although we require such service providers to safeguard any Personal Information received from us or collected on our behalf, we are not responsible or liable in any way for the acts or failure to act by any such service providers.

If you opt-in to receive newsletters, announcements, or advertisements of any kind from our business partners, we may share your Personal Information with such third parties, so that they can directly contact you regarding such offers. You may opt-out of any marketing offers from us or our business partners by informing us during your account sign-up process or through communications to us via email atsupport@mobogenie.com�Your opt-out does not apply to communications from The Company regarding any changes or updates to your account, or the non-marketing use of your Personal Information as described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information without notice if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Company; and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Website or the public.

What type of communications may I receive?

Special Offers and Updates

we will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice" section below.

Service-related Announcements

we will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Customer Service

based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

Recruit a Friend/E-cards

If you choose to use our recruit-a-friend or e-card features, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. The Company does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and to track the success of our referral program.

Who is collecting your information?

When you are asked for information while on The Company's site, you are sharing that information with The Company, its parent, and its various affiliates and sister companies, unless specifically stated otherwise. As a result of this sharing, you may receive communications from any of The Company's affiliates. In addition, some services are provided in conjunction with partner companies. If your personal information is being collected by another company other than The Company, you will be notified at the time the information is collected. If you do not want your information shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of information by not using that particular service or by not providing any information at that time.

Please be aware that we cannot control the activities of third parties to whom we provide data, and as such we cannot guarantee that they adhere to the same privacy and security procedures as The Company.

Please be aware that advertisers or websites with links to and from our sites may collect personal information about you. And remember, this Privacy Policy does not apply to, and cannot control the activities of, those other advertisers or websites.

With whom may your personal information be shared?

The Company may need to disclose your personal information to third party vendors to fulfill product orders or prizes, to process mailings, or to process, analyze, and/or store data on The Company's behalf. We will attempt to ensure that these entities do not use your personal information for any other purpose, and that they have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information they obtain from us. These service providers may not use your personal information for their own marketing purposes.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against you if you are violating the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for The Company's site or product, or may be causing injury to or interference (intentionally or unintentionally) with The Company's rights or property, other users of The Company's site or product, or anyone else who could be harmed by your activities. We also reserve the right to disclose your personal information if we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activities.

As with any business, your personal information is also an asset of The Company and will become part of our normal business records. As such, we may also disclose your personal information to a third party if we decide to sell a line of business to that third party, so you can continue to receive service and information in connection with that line of business with as little disruption as possible. Similarly, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, your personal information may be transferred to The Company's successor or assign.

The Company's sites may also have message boards, forums, and/or chat areas, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When posting to a message board, forum, or chat area, please be aware that the information is being made publicly available on-line and the user does so at his or her own risk. For certain forums, anyone posting or replying to a post may be doing so using their Real ID -- that is, their full first and last name - with the option to also display the name of their primary in-game character. See discussion regarding Real ID below. If your personal information is posted on one of our community forums, you may contact us at support@mobogenie.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

Opting Out

If at any point you wish to stop communication from our side please write to us at: support@mobogenie.com

Use of Cookies

The Website uses "cookies" to save you time and personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. A cookie tells the web server that you have returned to a specific page and helps the web server to recall your customized features. Information transmitted through cookies is not considered Personal Information unless it contains information that personally identifies you.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies; please refer to your web browser's instructions. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to experience certain interactive features of the Website.

We may use third parties to better understand your user preferences and deliver targeted advertisements to you. These third parties may also place cookies on your computer. This policy does not apply to, and The Company is not responsible for, cookies placed or data collected by such third parties.

Monitoring

We may, but are not obligated to, monitor and retain any and all data you transmit through our servers, including without limitation communications sent through or posted on the Website's discussion forums, chat rooms, and messaging functions, whether or not marked "private" by you. You acknowledge and agree that you have no expectation of privacy with respect to any such data transmitted, and you consent to any monitoring we may conduct.

Security of your Personal Information

We use commercially reasonable efforts to secure your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We also use industry-standard encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol, to protect certain kinds of information transmitted through the Website, such as your account password. Unfortunately, there are many factors beyond our control that could result in disclosure of Personal Information or any other information that you provide to us, and no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure, and we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to, the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Updating your Personal Information

You may review, correct, update, or delete your Personal Information maintained by us. Please provide us with sufficient proof of your identity and appropriate documentation of corrections to be made. You can contact us at: support@mobogenie.com

Please note that certain Personal Information, such as your date of birth or age, cannot be deleted from a user account unless you cancel your account. We also reserve the right to retain your Personal Information after account cancellation if such information is necessary to resolve any disputes or to comply with legal requirements.

Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy

You can contact mobogenie in relation to the privacy policy of "mobogenie" branded software or products, please submit a support request to customer support team, you can submit a support request to http://www.mobogenie.com/support
